Guide to the Partners for Livable Communities collection, 1962-1994
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 14: Oversize, 1967-1987; (2 boxes)
  - Urban design plan for the comprehensive plan of San Francisco, 1971 (Box 54, Volume 6)
  - Urban design program: centre city San Diego, 1981 (Box 54, Volume 7)
  - Urban design program: centre city San Diego, 1983 (Box 54, Volume 8)
  - Watershed: a new centre for the arts in Bristol, undated (Box 54, Volume 9)